if you're familiar with how gradients
如果您熟悉渐变是如何
work in inkscape then you probably
在Inkscape工作，那么你可能会
already know that you can take an object
我已经知道你可以拿着一个物体
and give it partial transparency
并使其具有部分透明度
by applying a gradient like that now as
通过将这样的渐变应用为
you can see the left-hand side of the
您可以在左侧看到
object still has all of its color
对象仍保持其所有颜色
whereas the right-hand side slowly
而右边慢慢地
transitions to transparency what if you
过渡到透明，如果您
wanted to do the same thing to a group
想对一群人做同样的事情
of objects though
尽管如此，
well if you select your group of objects
如果您选择您的对象组
and you try to apply
然后你试着申请
a gradient the same way you end up with
一个渐变，就像你最终得到的一样
something like this right here it's
像这样的东西就在这里
pretty safe to say that this is probably
可以很肯定地说，这很可能是
not the effect you're going for
不是你想要的效果
so how would you go about applying
那么你将如何着手申请呢？
partial transparency to this group of
对这组对象的部分透明度
objects like you did to this object
对象，就像您对此对象所做的那样
right here
就在这里
this is where opacity masks will come
这就是不透明面具的用武之地
into play and that's what i will be
投入到比赛中，这就是我将成为的人
demonstrating in this tutorial
本教程中的演示
this is nick with logosbynick.com and in
我是来自logosbynick.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create an opacity mask
您可以创建不透明蒙版
using inkscape before we get started
在开始之前使用Inkscape
though if you'd like to learn everything
不过，如果你想学到一切
that there is to know about inkscape
有关于Inkscape的知识
be sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where i go over every tool and
我看过每一个工具和
feature in inkscape
Inkscape中的功能
and i explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works i'll have a link in the
它是如何工作的，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out
看看这个
so to get us started here in inkscape as
所以为了让我们从Inkscape开始
you can see i have this selection of
你可以看到我有这个精选的
objects here if i
对象，如果我
click and drag over all of them this is
单击并拖动所有这些选项，这就是
uh this entire design consists of a
呃，整个设计包括一个
bunch of individual objects
一串单独的对象
i'm going to go ahead and group them
我将继续对它们进行分组
together using this button right here
一起使用这里的按钮
that says group selected objects
这表示对选定对象进行分组
and what i want to do is apply an
我想要做的是应用一个
opacity mask to this
不透明蒙版到此
so that i can have partial transparency
这样我就可以有部分透明度
so to do that let me first open up the
要做到这一点，让我首先打开
fill and stroke menu which is over here
在这里的填充和描边菜单
you can click on this or you can go to
您可以点击此链接，也可以访问
object
对象
fill and stroke and that will open up
填充和笔触，这将打开
that menu right here okay
菜单就在这里，好的
so what i'm going to do is i'm going to
所以我要做的是我要
use the masking feature instead of
使用屏蔽功能，而不是
applying a linear gradient like i would
像我这样应用线性渐变
with an individual object
使用单个对象
i'm going to use the masking feature
我将使用屏蔽功能
instead okay and the way
相反，好的和方法
masking works is that you take an object
伪装的工作原理是你拿着一个物体
and you apply it over the group of
并将其应用于一组
objects
对象
and whatever whenever the object is
无论什么时候，只要物体
black it becomes transparent on the
它在黑色上变得透明
group of objects but when it's white it
一组物体，但当它是白色的时候
becomes opaque
变得不透明
it's a lot easier for me to demonstrate
对我来说演示要容易得多
how this works and it is to explain it
它是如何工作的，它是如何解释它的
so let me go ahead and do that i'm going
所以让我继续吧，我要走了
to grab the squares and rectangles tool
抓取正方形和矩形工具的步骤
and i'm going to click and drag to
我要点击并拖动到
create a rectangle covering the entire
创建一个覆盖整个
subject here
主题在此
and what i'm going to do is i'm going to
我要做的是我要
make this black and i'm going to give
把这个弄黑，我就会给你
this a linear gradient with this button
这是使用此按钮的线性渐变
right here
就在这里
and i'm going to click on this stop on
我要点击这一站
the right hand side and i'm just going
右手边，我要走了
to make that white so we have a gradient
把它变成白色，这样我们就有了渐变
going from black
从黑色走到
to white like this now how this works is
像这样的白色现在是如何运作的
what when i take
如果我拿了
this object right here and apply it as a
这个对象就在这里，并将其作为
mask
遮罩
to the group of objects beneath it
到它下面的一组对象
whatever is black
不管什么是黑色的
will become transparent and whatever is
会变得透明，不管是什么
white will remain opaque
白色将保持不透明
okay so let me show you what i mean here
好的，让我告诉你我在这里的意思
let me grab the select tool
让我拿一下选择工具
let me click and drag over both of these
让我在这两个上面单击并拖动
objects my grouping of objects
对象我的对象分组
as well as the mask that i created here
以及我在这里制作的面具
with this rectangle
用这个矩形
i can go to object mask
我可以转到对象遮罩
set and as you can see there's some
套装，如你所见，这里有一些
partial transparency here
此处部分透明
over here on the right hand side was the
在这里的右手边是
color white so this is more visible
涂成白色，这样更容易看得见
whereas over here is the color black so
而这里是黑色，所以
this becomes more transparent
这变得更加透明
now if you want to alter this further
现在，如果您想进一步更改此设置
you can go to object mask
您可以转到对象蒙版
release and let me click off of that to
松开鼠标，让我点击一下
deselect everything let me click on just
取消选择所有内容，让我只点击
this object right here and i'm going to
这个物体就在这里，我要
grab the gradient tool which is right
抓住右边的渐变工具
here
这里
and i'm going to move this white stop in
我要把这个白色的停靠点搬到
like this and i'm going to move this
像这样，我要把这个移开
black stop in like this and i'm holding
黑色就这样停了下来，我抱着
ctrl when i do this to lock it onto the
当我这样做时按Ctrl键将其锁定在
horizontal axis
水平轴
now if i go back to the select tool and
现在如果我返回到选择工具并
i select both of those objects and go to
我选择了这两个对象并转到
object mask set as you can see
对象蒙版设置，如您所见
the right hand side of this is more
右手边是更多
visible now because there was more white
现在看得见，因为有更多的白色
included in that
包括在那里面
mask whereas the left hand side is more
蒙版，而左侧则更多
transparent because there was more
透明，因为有更多
black included in that mask and a tip
面具中包括黑色和一条提示
one helpful tip for how you can go about
一个有用的小贴士，教你如何行动
adjusting this better what i'm going to
更好地调整这一点，我将
do is i'm going to release this
我要做的就是发布这个
object mask release what you can do
对象遮罩释放您可以执行的操作
is you can take this object right here
你可以把这个物体放在这里
and bring the opacity down a little bit
并将不透明度降低一点
so you can see exactly where the black
所以你可以准确地看到黑色的
and white lines up
和白色的线条
so if i take that and i go back to the
所以如果我拿着它，我回到
gradient tool i can take this white stop
渐变工具我可以选择这个白色停靠点
and put it
然后把它放在
directly in the middle like this and i
就在中间，就像这样和我
can take this black stop and put it
可以把这个黑色的止损放在
almost next to it like that and now what
就在它旁边，就像那样，现在怎么办
i can do is go back to the select tool
我能做的就是返回到选择工具
take the object take the mask and bring
拿着物体拿着面具，带着
the opacity of it all the way back up
它的不透明一直向上
if you apply the mask with partial
如果使用Partial应用遮罩
transparency you're going to have
你会有一个透明的
partial opacity in your object which is
对象中的部分不透明度
not what you're looking for so
不是你想要的，所以
make sure to bring that opacity all the
一定要把这种不透明带到
way back up click and drag over
返回原点并单击并拖动
both objects object mask
两个对象对象遮罩
set and there you go and i think that
布景，就是这样，我想
should do it for this lesson that is how
为了这一课应该这样做，这就是为什么
you can go about creating an
您可以着手创建一个
opacity mask with inkscape and by the
不透明蒙版与Inkscape和
way this doesn't just work with linear
这种方法不仅适用于线性
gradients this can work
渐变这是可行的
with a radial gradient as well i'll show
使用径向渐变，我也会展示
you that real quick i'm going to choose
你真的那么快，我要选择
a radial gradient
径向梯度
and let's go ahead and apply it again
让我们继续应用它
object mask
对象掩模
set and as you can see the center where
设置，正如您所看到的中心，
the black was became transparent where
黑色变得透明，
the outside
外部
became fully opaque one last thing i
变得完全不透明我的最后一件事
want to show you though before i end
想在我结束之前向你展示
this video
这个视频
you can take your object go to the
你可以把你的物品带到
gradient tool and you can click on
渐变工具，您可以点击
i believe it's this button right here
我相信就是这里的这个按钮
reverse the direction of the
扭转方向
gradient let's say you want the outside
梯度假设您想要外部
to be black and the inside to be white
黑色，内部白色
just click that button right there and
只需点击那里的按钮，
it reverses it for you
它会为您扭转局面
and now you can click and drag over both
现在您可以单击并拖动两者
of it go to object
其中的一部分转到对象
mask set and there you go and that
面具设置好了，就这样了
should do it for this tutorial that is
应该在本教程中这样做，即
how you can go about easily creating
如何轻松创建
an opacity mask using inkscape if you
如果您使用水墨景观，则使用不透明度面膜
have any questions leave a comment below
有任何问题请在下面留言
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
[Music]
[音乐]